

# **INFORMATION**

Date of Birth 22 January 1999

Adress Grabijnhof 21 2625LL, Delft Netherlands

Phone +31 6 58 94 44 75

Email karlijnsanders5@gmail.com

Nationality Dutch

Language Dutch, Englisch, Norwegian

Drivers license AM, A, B

# **COMPETENCES**

Photoshop
Indesign
Figma

Illustrator
Powerpoint

Excel

## **EDUCATIONS**

Master Strategic Product Design Industrial Design Engineering TU Delft (2022-now)

Bachelor Industrial Design Engineering TU Delft (2018-2021)

Criminology short HBO (2022)

Folkhøgeskule Hallingdal, Norway (2017-2018)

Techansium Christelijk Lyceum Delft (2011-2017) (NG +NT)

# Karlijn Marie Sanders

## **PROFILE**

Currently I am in the first year of the Master's degree Strategic Product Design at Industrial Design at TU Delft. I run nominally with my studies and get a lot of motivation from the group assignments that I can tackle with an international team. Before I started my bachelor's degree Industrial Design Engineer in Delft, I lived in Norway for a year. I went to a Folkhøgeskule. Here I practiced a lot of outdoor sports and joined group projects. Being surrounded by people gives me a lot of energy, which is why I really enjoy working together. On the other hand, working independently is also one of my strengths. I always take my responsibilities. I am also curious and I enjoy learning new things. My creativity and entrepreneurship often ensure that I have small projects running or that I come up with new solutions for day to day problems.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Teaching assistant TU Delft, Industrial Design Engineering:** August 2020-present Being a teaching assistant at the faculty of Industrial Design Engineering is one of the most wonderful jobs there is. I am preparing workshops and assist the first year's students. Helping other students with knowledge I learned just a few years ago at the same faculty is something I am proud of to share with others. I really like the interaction with the new students.

#### Secrid wallets: August-November 2021

The Dutch Industrial Design company Secrid wallets has been a pleasure to work for. I have been working on a sustainable way of repairing wallets and creating a more enjoyable customer experience. I also worked at the customer care.

#### Marketing agency Blauwe Monsters: 2019 -present

Currently I am working for Blauwe Monsters. This is a marketing agency, I am writing blogs for their customers. I learn a lot about different products and environments

#### Promotion team of faculty Industrial Design Engineering 2019-2021

I worked in the promotion team of Industrial Design Engineering. I helped on open days and I provided future students with walk along days and try to help them in their choice of study.

#### **B&B Pensão das Duna:** 2017 & 2019

For two summers I have been working in a B&B (Pensão das Duna) in Portugal. Guest came from all over the world. I was able to immediately improve my communication skills. The fact that the owner gave me so much responsibility was exciting but also a nice challenge. This required quite a bit of organizational skills.

## Water skipark Wollebrand: 2018

I worked at the water ski park Wollebrand for a few months. I arranged all registrations and timeslots for the customers. I was also in charge of the technical part of the water ski park with my colleagues. It was important that I worked precisely.

Babysitting: 2015-present

## **HOBBIES**

## CORE VALUES

- Traveling - Creative projects

- Sailing - Crossfit

- Snowboarding - Cooking

- Social

- Resposible

- Crossfit - Motivated

rated - Inquisitive

- Teamworker

- Creative